#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/samuelerube-976601204 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

React.js Amazon Web Services (AWS) Docker

# Samuel Erube

Full Stack Software Engineer | Backend Engineer | Frontend Engineer | PHP | MySQL | MSSQL | PostgresSQL | Javascript | Node.js | Typescript | Vue.js | React.js | ReactNative Lagos State, Nigeria

## Summary

I am a creative, reliable, and proficient Full Stack Software Engineer with 7+ years of experience and devotion to delivering the most exciting and challenging IT projects.

I'm experienced in developing web and mobile applications (Laravel, Codeigniter, Javascript, NodeJS, iOS, Android, NativeScript, ReactNative), managing databases (MySql, MSSQL, Postgresql), and designing user interfaces (VueJs, ReactJs, Jquery/Ajax/React Query/Axios, CSS, HTML5, Bootstrap, Semantic UI) with apt knowledge of user experience.

I possess excellent interpersonal skills, enabling great interaction with a wide range of clients and teams and a productive team player, able to motivate and increase a team-focused culture.

# Experience

onehealthng.com Software Engineer June 2023 - Present (8 months) Lagos State, Nigeria

Vendease (YC W21)
Backend Engineer
August 2022 - February 2023 (7 months)
Lagos State, Nigeria

Turing.com
Software Engineer
May 2021 - February 2023 (1 year 10 months)

- Created well tested and aesthetically pleasing web applications.
- Experimented with innovative technologies and novel approaches to tackle challenging technical problems.

- Collaborated with an agile cross-functional team of both industry specialists and developers.

### Freelance

Full Stack Developer January 2021 - February 2023 (2 years 2 months)

### MTK Consults

7 years 2 months

Full Stack Developer

January 2016 - February 2022 (6 years 2 months)

Lagos, Nigeria

MTK Consulting is a software development company that aims at delivering maximum quality services to customers all around the globe:

Full Stack Developer January 2015 - December 2015 (1 year) Lagos, Nigeria

### Paygital

Senior Software Engineer December 2019 - December 2020 (1 year 1 month)

### Education

Yaba College of Technology, Yaba, Lagos HND, Computer Science · (2011 - 2017)